Kosuke Futsukaichi

thekosuke.com thekosuke@icloud.com 604 339 2981 Kosuke (ko-skay) is a product and experience designer currently based in Vancouver. With a multi-cultural lens, he strives to craft and deliver meaningful value through digital offerings that extend beyond their functional purpose.

STATUS -

Graduation Date: June 2020 Seeking graduate positions

COMPETENCIES -

UX Research
Experience Strategy
UX/UI Design
Interaction Design
Visual Design
Motion Design
Digital Prototyping
Front-End Development

AWARDS -

People's Choice Award

2017 · Vancouver UX Awards

Regional Champion

2017 · Enactus Canada

First Place Recipient

2016 · Seattle Design Charette

First Place Recipient

2015 · Canon Canada Photography

EDUCATION -

Simon Fraser University

B.A. · Interaction Design Sept. 2014 - June 2020

italiaDesign Field School

Spring/Summer 2018

EXPERIENCES

Design Intern @ Green Stone

Present

Currently an intern at Green Stone, a product design and strategy firm with a remote-first model.

Experience Design Intern @ R/GA TYO

Summer 2019

Collaborated with multidisciplinary teams on various client work for Shiseido, Google, and other undisclosed clients. Projects include concepting for retail experience, facilitating ideation workshops, crafting the UX for Google's B2B platforms, and prototyping for a client pitch.

Product Designer (Contract) @ Instaread

Fall 2018

Supported the company as a freelance design consultant primarily focused on product design and art direction.

Notable projects include: redesigning the Onboarding and Subscription page for iOS, numerous optimizations for the Web app, and creating the App Preview for the App Store.

UX/UI Designer (Contract) @ The Digital Panda

Spring 2018

Supported the team by creating wireframes and designing visuals for multiple client projects.

VOLUNTEER -

Designer/Developer · Touchpoint IxD Conference

Spring 2019

Created the visual identity and designed/developed the conference website for Touchpoint 2019.

Design Mentor · Seattle Design Charrette

2017-2019

Participated as a group mentor for a second-year spatial design couse during a weekend long design charrette to guide students through the design process.

Graphic Designer · Enactus SFU

2016 - 2017

Volunteered to be the graphic designer for the Bright Ideas program. I was responsible for redesigning the website and collaborating with the marketing manager to create promotional materials.